place_value = {
    "Definition": "Place value refers to the value that each digit in a number has, based on its position. For example, in the number 523, the 5 is in the hundreds place, the 2 is in the tens place, and the 3 is in the ones place.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "What value does the 4 represent in the number 2466?",
                "Answer": "400",
                "Type": "Integer",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }

expanded_form = {
    "Definition": "Expanded form breaks a number down to show the value of each digit. For example, 724 can be written in expanded form as 700 + 20 + 4",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Which expression is equivalent to 56,900?",
                "Answer": "50000 + 6000 + 900",
                "Type": "",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }

written_form = {
    "Definition": "Written form uses words to write out a number. For example, 724 can be written in written form as 'seven hundred twenty-four.'",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "What is 9,421 in words?",
                "Answer": "Nine thousand, four hundred twenty-one",
                "Type": "String",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }

regrouping = {
    "Definition": "Regrouping whole number place values refers to the process of rearranging the digits in a number according to their place \
    value positions, such as tens, hundreds, thousands, and so on, in order to simplify calculations or represent the number in a different form. \
    It involves shifting digits from one place value position to another while maintaining the overall value of the number.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "What is 4 hundreds plus 7 tens",
                "Answer": "470",
                "Type": "Integer",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

round_whole_number = {
    "Definition": "Rounding is one way of estimating. When we round, we adjust a number to the nearest 'round' number \
    (like the nearest ten, hundred, or thousand). Estimating can also involve guessing or using other strategies to come up with an approximate answer.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Round 2826 to the nearest hundred.",
                "Answer": "2800",
                "Type": "Integer",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

dis_property = {
    "Definition": "The distributive property is a rule in math that lets us break apart a multiplication problem into smaller parts to make it easier to multiply.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Multiply 123*6 by using the distributive property",
                "Answer": "123*6=(100+20+3)*6=(100*6)+(20*6)+(3*6)=(600)+(120)+(18)=738",
                "Type": "String",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

interpret_remainders = {
    "Definition": "When we divide one number by another, sometimes the division doesn't come out evenly. The remainder is the part that's left over.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Gracie has 5 pet bunnies that love to eat whole carrots. \
                She has 39 carrots to feed the bunnies. Gracie will use as many carrots as she can and give each bunny the same number.\
                How many carrots remain without being given to a bunny?",
                "Answer": "4",
                "Type": "Integer",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  


factors = {
    "Definition": "Factors are the numbers that divide evenly into a larger number",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Which equation shows that 6 is a factor of 18?",
                "Answer": "3=18/6",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

multiples = {
    "Definition": "Factors are the numbers that divide evenly into a larger number",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Which equation best shows that 30 is a multiple of 10?",
                "Answer": "30=10*3",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

prime = {
    "Definition": "A prime number is a number that can only be divided evenly by itself and 1. For example, 2, 3, 5, 7, and 11 are all prime numbers.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Which of these numbers is prime? 18, 41, 45,77, 93",
                "Answer": "30=10*3",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

composite = {
    "Definition": "A composite number is a number that has more than two factors. For example, 6 is a composite number because it has the factors 1, 2, 3, and 6.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Is each number prime or composite? 5, 9, 57",
                "Answer": "5 is prime, 9 and 57 are composite",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

equi_fraction = {
    "Definition": "Equivalent fractions are fractions that represent the same part of a whole, even though they look different. For example, 1/2 and 2/4 fraction are equivalent fractions because they both represent half of a whole.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "k/100 = 1/10. What number could replace k",
                "Answer": "10",
                "Type": "Integer",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

common_denominators = {
    "Definition": "Common denominators are when two or more fractions have the same denominator (the bottom number in a fraction). To use a common denominator, you can find equivalent fractions for both fractions so that they both have the same denominator.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "What is the least common denominator for the two fractions 2/5 and 3/2?",
                "Answer": "10",
                "Type": "Integer",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

comparing_fractions = {
    "Definition": "To compare fractions with unlike denominators, you can either use a common denominator or use benchmarks.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Katie made a list to show how much time she spent on homework last week. The list: Math:3/4, Reading: 7/8, Writing: 3/6, Science: 5/10 .On which activities did Katie spend more than 2/3 hour?",
                "Answer": "Math and Reading",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

addsub_fractions = {
    "Definition": "To add fractions with common denominators, we keep the denominator the same and add the numerators together.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "James and Karlee caught a lizard in their backyard. Its length from head to the end of the tail is 3/5 meters, and the length of its tail is 1/5 meters. What is the length of the lizard without the tail?",
                "Answer": "3/5 - 1/5 = 2/5 meters",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

mixed_numbers = {
    "Definition": "A mixed number is a combination of a whole number and a fraction. For example, 2 1/2",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Archer made a tunnel for his hamster out of two cardboard tubes. One tube was 8 5/8 in long. The other tube was 7 6/8 long. What is the total length of the tunnel?",
                "Answer": "8 5/8 +  7 6/8= 15 11/8 inches",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

efwnmp = {
    "Definition": "Multiply fractions and whole numbers word problems",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "The pepper plant has 2/3 as many fruits on it as the tomato plant has. The tomato plant has 9 fruits on it. How many fruits does the pepper plant have on it?",
                "Answer": "2/3 * 9 = 6 fruits",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  

decimal = {
    "Definition": " A decimal is another way of expressing a part of a whole, using a decimal point. For example, 0.5 also means 'one half.'",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "How can we write 5.04 in words?",
                "Answer": "Five and four hundredths",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  


uam = {
    "Definition": "There are three main types of angles: acute (less than 90 degrees), right (90 degrees), and obtuse (more than 90 degrees).",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "∠PQR∠, P, Q, R is a right angle. Which of the following could be its measure?",
                "Answer": "90 degrees",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }  
decompose_angle = {
    "Definition": "When we decompose an angle, we break it down into smaller angles that add up to the original angle.",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "A stunt man wants to drive a car off a ramp at an angle of 35 degrees from the ground. He already has a ramp with an angle of 5 degrees. He plans to add a second ramp on top to increase the angle to 35 degrees. What angle measure does the second ramp need to have?",
                "Answer": "30 - 15 = 20 degrees",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }   
aap = {
    "Definition": "Area and perimeter",
    "QA Queue": [
            {
                "Question": "Mike built a rectangular dog pen that is 21 feet long and has a perimeter of 78 feet. What is the width of Mike's dog pen?",
                "Answer": "(78-21-21)/2=18 feet",
                "Type": "Narrative",
                "Difficulty": 2
            }
        ],
    "Rate": 1,
    }   

grade_4_part_1 = {
    "Place value": [
        {
            "introduction to place value": place_value
        },
        {
            "Writing whole numbers in expanded form": expanded_form
        },
        {
            "Writing whole numbers in written form": written_form
        },
        # {
        #     "Regrouping whole number place values": regrouping
        # }
    ],
    "Addition, subtraction, and estimation": [
        {
            "Rounding whole numbers": round_whole_number
        }
    ],
    "Multiply by 1-digit numbers": [
        {
            "Multiply 3- and 4-digits by 1-digit with distributive property": dis_property
        },
    ],
    "Division":[
        {
            "Interpret remainders":interpret_remainders
        }
    ],
    "Factors, multiples and patterns":[
        {
            "Identify factors": factors,
        },
        {
            "Identify multiples": multiples,
        },
        {
            "Prime numbers": prime
        },
        {
            "Composite numbers": composite
        }
    ],
    "Equivalent fractions and comparing fractions":[
        {
            "Equivalent fractions": equi_fraction
        },
        {
            "Common denominators": common_denominators
        },
        {
            "Comparing fractions with unlike denominators": comparing_fractions
        }
    ],
    "Add and subtract fractions": [
        {
            "Adding and subtracting fractions: word problems": addsub_fractions
        },
        {
            "Mixed numbers": mixed_numbers
        }
    ],
    "Multiply fractions": [
        {
            "Equivalent fraction and whole number multiplication problems": efwnmp
        }
    ],

    "Understand decimals": [
        {
            "Decimals in words": decimal
        }

    ],

    "Measuring angles": [
        {
            "Understanding angle measurement": uam
        },
        {
            "Decompose angles": decompose_angle
        }
    ],

    "Area and perimeter": [
        {
            "Area and perimeter": aap
        }
    ]

}